<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 20:09:51 +0600</pubDate><title><![CDATA[About]]></title><url><![CDATA[index_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[ZERE Construction Company, mobile modular buildings, fields, Kazakhstan, Balkhash]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[Turnkey construction of high-quality pre-fabricated modular buildings, block containers of any complexity and configuration for the fields, remote locations, highly specialized work shift]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template-main.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;ZERE&amp;quot; Construction Company &amp;ndash; Manufacturers of mobile modular buildings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	The Company was established in 2007. During this period the Company has garnered a wide range of experience in building modular buildings, camp set-ups, warehousing units etc. and can work to fulfill any required scope of work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	Our company is located in Republic of Kazakhstan in Balkhash city, Karaganda region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	The Company has well developed infrastructure; equipment, the industrial premises convenient to access roads. The manufacturing facility is located within the city boundaries and encompasses a total area over 20000 square meters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	The advantages and features of our production services you can review in the &lt;a href=&quot;/production/&quot;&gt;Production&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	Projects we have undertaken and or participated in can be reviewed in the &lt;a href=&quot;/projects/&quot;&gt;Projects&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify&quot;&gt;
	All necessary requisites and information regarding the Company please find in &lt;a href=&quot;/contacts/&quot;&gt;Contacts&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu></item>
