<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 22:00:16 +0600</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Modular unit prefabrication]]></title><url><![CDATA[module-block-specification_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[Technical specification, Modular unit prefabrication, FRAME, FLOOR, EXTERNAL and INTERNAL WALLS, INTERNAL PARTITIONS, CEILING, ROOF TRUSSES, FLOORING, DOORS, WINDOWS, ELECTRICAL, TELEPHONE, INTERNET, TELEVISION, Satellite, HVAC, PLUMBING]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[Technical specification - Modular unit prefabrication]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Technical specification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;FRAME&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Frame of a modular unit is manufactured using angle iron according to GOST 8509-86, c-channel according to GOST 8240-89, 2mm width profile sheets according to GOST 19903-74.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;FLOOR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The floor is insulated using 150mm R1.50M2 kW fibreglass. High quality plywood is screwed down with self-tapping screws to intermediate steel cross sections. Flooring applied on plywood is chosen by client.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Bathroom floor is high quality plywood with rubberised material sealant Flooring is chosen by client. (e.g. &amp;ndash; linoleum).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;EXTERNAL/INTERNAL WALLS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Nominal thickness of external walls is 100mm. Internal carcass is manufactured 100mm. wooden studs, preliminary treated with fireproof liquid and placed at 450mm CRS. Metal external studs are placed at 1000mm CRS. All internal carcass joints are screwed with self-tapping screws to internal steel frame. The exterior is panelled with Mic welding. Thickness of profile panelling is 1.0mm steel panelling is of high quality and strength. Colour exterior grey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All internal/external steel works will be cleaned and primed with one coat of steel primer paint and two coats of outside paint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;INTERNAL PARTITIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Nominal thickness of internal walls will be 100mm. Internal wall panel will be faced with 8mm-laminate d&amp;eacute;cor panel. (client&amp;rsquo;s chose).&lt;br /&gt;
	Wall panels will be insulated with 100mm R1.50M2 kW Fibreglass with 150g vapour barrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;CEILING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Plywood of high quality is fixed to steel structure with steel self-tapping screws, ceiling laminate to be installed to plywood. Insulation will comprise of 1.50mm R1.50M2 KW Fibreglass with 150g vapour barrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;ROOF TRUSSES &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All roof trusses will be constructed using high quality steel. Roof trusses will be pitched to the minimum local building norms (300mm). All roof trusses to be cleaned and primed with 1 coats of steel primer paint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Roofing will be a profile panel 0,7mm sheet .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;FLOORING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Floors will be of client choice. e.g. carpet,linoleum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;DOORS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Doors will comprise of the following types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		800mmx2000mm wood solid core c/w lock set.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		600mmx2000mm solid c/w lock set.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		900mmx2000mm metal exterior door c/w lock with handles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;WINDOWS&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All windows will be UPVC single framed, double-glazed opening dimensions 1100mm x 900mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;ELECTRICAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The electrical installation shall consist of general lighting, heating, a/c, water boilers and other KW loads.&lt;br /&gt;
	Lighting will consist of incandescent luminaries in accommodation units and fluorescent twin lamp fittings installed in office, dining and other public areas. Fluorescent fittings installed in areas prone to moisture will be IP 65 Rated. All other fluorescent luminaries will be complete with prismatic acrylic diffusers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Three phase supplies can be included for all areas if required once loadings are defined.&lt;br /&gt;
	Each main building will have individual main distribution panel with main breaker suitably sized. All sub panels will be terminated into main distribution panels controlling all necessary KW requirements. Each sub panel will supply three phase 380/240 volt-50Hertz. All panel breakers to be identified in English/Russian&lt;br /&gt;
	Each consumer unit is fed via a double sheathed three-phase supply cable, size calculated by KW.&lt;br /&gt;
	Cable installation will consist of PVC trunking surface mounted or in finished walls. Main cable runs will be installed using cable trays above ceilings in corridor areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;TELEPHONE/ INTERNET/ TELEVISION (Satellite)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	To be installed where necessary. (As per Client&amp;rsquo;s request and preference).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;HVAC&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All units will be provided with wall mounted or standing Heating and Cooling air-condition systems where necessary, in accommodation units only cooling. Depending on the room size these will be either 800 watt or 1200watt capacity. As well as wall mounted electric heaters/with thermostat control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;PLUMBING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Hot and cold water lines are type PVC with shut off valves at each fixture.&lt;br /&gt;
	All waste pipes are schedule PVC.&lt;br /&gt;
	All pipe work will be boxed type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All sanitary ware will be quality standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Each unit will have its own piping, with connection to a major gathering point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	/pbr /&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu></item>
