<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 21:52:36 +0600</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Products]]></title><url><![CDATA[production_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[50 1000 man camps, office units, hotels, houses, hunting fishing lodges, first-aid clinics hospitals, dormitories, dining rooms, shower and laundry units, accommodation units, workshops, warehouses for materials and tools, baths, saunas, toilets, check-points,guard houses, modular buildings for laboratories, block modules for security firms, block modules for retail offices, refrigeration units, skid manufacture]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[Turnkey construction of high-quality pre-fabricated modular buildings, block containers of any complexity and configuration for the fields, remote locations, highly specialized work shift]]></metad><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template-product.php]]></template><content><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Manufacture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Production units offered by &amp;quot;ZERE&amp;quot; Construction Company are made utilizing existing standard steel 20-foot railway and 40-foot sea containers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The accommodation unit is the finished building with steel and painted sheeting possessing high anticorrosive properties. External corners, windows and doorways are finished with steel. At customer&amp;rsquo;s request the units can be finished in various color combinations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The internal lay-out and furnishing of the units will be designed and fitted out as per your requirements. Highly skilled employees of our company work to European standards of construction and finishing, to include sanitary requirements to applicable standards. Following completion of the units in our facility our personnel will execute installation and assembly on location.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Execution variants&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Our mobile buildings can be manufactured as one off buildings or multiple accommodation units as per your requirements in both one and two story configurations. Units will be fitted with sanitary requirements as per your spec . Kitchen units, toilet and shower units, laundry facilities along with the required heating, air conditioning and insulation are also provided as per your requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Advantages of mobile containerized buildings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Buildings are transported by truck and or rail to any required destination. If required the units can be easily disassembled for transportation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The design and construction of the modules provides for a high degree of fire-prevention protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	As per spec requirements mobile buildings can provide for independent life-support i.e. water and electric power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Application of modern advanced finishing materials allows for the units esthetic external and internal qualities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Units offered for various applications: Accommodation, laundry, kitchen/canteen, toilets/showers, recreational rooms, warehouses and any auxiliary industrial buildings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Distinctive features of our manufactured buildings are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Delivery time for construction and commissioning;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Competitive pricing and quality;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Containerized units weight allows for less time and expense for foundation works;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		High quality characteristics;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Durability;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Units can be fully operational at ambient temperatures from-35 C to +50 C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;ZERE&amp;quot; Construction Company&amp;rdquo; produces the following:&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		50-1000 man camps;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Office units;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Hotels, houses, hunting/fishing lodges;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		First-aid clinics and hospitals;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Dormitories;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Dining rooms;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Shower and laundry units;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Accommodation units&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Workshops;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Warehouses for materials and tools;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Baths, saunas;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Toilets/shower;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Check-points / Guard Houses;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Modular buildings for laboratories;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Block modules for security firms;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Block modules for retail offices etc. ;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Refrigeration Units;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		Skid manufacture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Technical specification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/module-block-specification/&quot;&gt;Modular unit prefabrication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/container-specification/&quot;&gt;Converted container&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><private><![CDATA[]]></private><menu><![CDATA[]]></menu></item>
