<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 19:35:48 +0600</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Converted container]]></title><url><![CDATA[container-spec_en]]></url><meta><![CDATA[Technical specification, Converted container, FLOOR, EXTERNAL and INTERNAL WALLS, INTERNAL PARTITIONS, CEILING, FLOOR COVERINGS, DOORS, WINDOWS, ELECTRICAL, TELEPHONE, INTERNET, TELEVISION, Satellite, HVAC, PLUMBING]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[Technical specification - Converted container]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Converted container]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;Technical specification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;FLOOR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The floor is insulated using 150mm R1.50M2 kW fibreglass. Metal profile panelling is installed by a process of Mic welding and primed with one coat of metal prime.&lt;br /&gt;
	Flooring is linoleum (up to client&amp;rsquo;s choice).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Bathroom floor is high quality plywood with rubberised material sealant Flooring is linoleum ( chosen by client.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;EXTERNAL/INTERNAL WALLS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Nominal thickness is 100mm. Internal walls are of timber, preliminarily finished with fireproof liquid. Studs will be placed at 450mm CRS. All carcass joints will be screwed with self-tapping screws to internal frame. Colour exterior grey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All internal/external steel works will be cleaned and primed with 1 coats of steel primer paint and 2 coats of outside paint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Internal face will be finished with 8mm-laminate d&amp;eacute;cor panel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;INTERNAL PARTITIONS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Nominal thickness of internal walls will be 100mm. Internal wall panel will be faced with 8mm-laminate d&amp;eacute;cor panel. (Client Chose).&lt;br /&gt;
	Insulation with 100mm R1.50M2 kW Fibreglass with 150g vapour barrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;CEILING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Сeiling laminate to be installed to plywood chosen by client. Insulation will comprise of 1.50mm R1.50M2 KW Fibreglass with 150g vapour barrier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;FLOOR COVERINGS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Floors will be linoleum or client chose. E.g. Carpet, laminate, vinyl or tile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;DOORS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Doors will comprise of the following types.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		800mmx2000mm wood solid core c/w lock set.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		600mmx2000mm wood solid core c/w lock set.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		900mmx2000mm exterior door with door lock/ handles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;WINDOWS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All windows will be UPVC single framed, double-glazed opening dimensions 1200mm x 900mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;ELECTRICAL &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The electrical installation shall consist of general lighting, heating, a/c, water boilers and other KW loads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Lighting will consist of incandescent luminaries in accommodation units and fluorescent twin lamp fittings installed in office, dining and other public areas. Fluorescent fittings installed in areas prone to moisture will be IP 65 Rated. All other fluorescent luminaries will be complete with prismatic acrylic diffusers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Three phase supplies can be included for all areas if required once loadings are defined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Each main building will have individual main distribution panel with main breaker suitably sized. All sub panels will be terminated into main distribution panels controlling all necessary KW requirements. Each sub panel will supply three phase 380/220 volt-50Hertz. All panel breakers to be identified in English/Russian&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Each consumer unit is fed via a double sheathed three-phase supply cable, size calculated by KW.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Cable installation in finished walls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;TELEPHONE/ INTERNET/ TELEVISION (Satellite)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	To be installed where necessary. (As per Client&amp;rsquo;s request and preference).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;HVAC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All units will be provided with wall mounted Cooling air-condition systems where necessary. Depending on the room size these will be either 800 watt or 1200watt capacity. As well as wall mounted electric heaters/with thermostat control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;strong&gt;PLUMBING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Hot and cold water lines are type PVC with shut off valves at each fixture.&lt;br /&gt;
	All waste pipes are schedule PVC.&lt;br /&gt;
	All pipe work will be boxed type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	All sanitary ware will be good quality standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Each unit will have its own piping, with connection to a major gathering point.&lt;/p&gt;
]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private></item>
